good afternoon Bashar and do you good
day how are you perfect and you uh good
I actually brought a little show and
tell and um I find something very
synchronistic about today yes uh we were
just talking about free energy and yes
uh we were talking last Channel last uh
public channeling about a double helip
cone fitting into itself yes um and you
have begun to experiment yes I've begun
to experiment and actually brought one
and
um I just received this I had the a
model made
yes uh a couple of days ago I just
received it yes a couple of days ago um
and I'll show hold it up so everybody
can see it just a cone with this uh kind
of a spiral around it yes and had a
computer model this and then a machine
actually make this yes well this is the
template for the construction of the
conductive material exactly this is a
jig that I wrap Accord around yes and so
I've done that I just did this yesterday
day before yesterday oh all right and
it's basically two uh coils kind of Spun
into each other yes exactly as you were
describing yes well not exactly because
they're not insulated yet that's correct
and in fact I bought the insulated paint
day before yesterday so my next
step um but I find the synchronicity so
interesting because I've been working on
this kind of on and off for the past
several months and just day before
yesterday I received it in the mail yes
so thank you for your synchronicity
hours later I wrapped this thing
together and the next day I'm showing up
here at the channeling so there you go
it's so interesting so my question for
you and I don't want to get too
technically now I will on at a private
but uh my question for you is basically
how does this thing
work what is it what what is it doing
what what am I okay so I've got these
coils they they're round you know
wrapped into each other
um it is in some degree the essence of
what you
call a capacitor and a
Transformer okay the idea is that once
you initiate a certain kind of
electrical current through
it you allow it to become vibrationally
sensitive because of its shape to higher
frequency energies which are then in a
sense harmonically attracted to it and
begin coursing along the same route once
the higher frequency energies begin
coursing along the same route it sets up
a self-reinforcing
vibration that then can be Amplified in
a variety of ways and transformed
stepped down and transformed into
electrical energy or various kinds of
energy that you can tap and use for your
devices on your planet okay so basically
I need to Kickstart it with uh a pulse
an AC pulse or a DC Cur probably an AC
pulse yes and then it'll start
resonating yes and it will in a sense
drive itself yes from which I can then
start tapping energy off of that yes um
now now now now this is the very
beginning this is the very early
experimentation form this will improve
and this will become more sophisticated
but first it is necessary to do the
experimentations at this level in order
to then see that you're getting some
effect which will then guide you to the
next stage of refining it on that note
there are actually quite a number of V
inventors out there that have devices
that are at the very beginning stages
that actually show anomalous quote
unquote anomalous Yes Energy being
generated it's already out there that
this stuff already exists yes I know and
they're still they're in the basic
stages so they're figuring things out
just like iy am you know so and this is
the essani approach
ah got it okay then what one last
question on this what is then the energy
that it's resonating with you said a
higher frequency energy yes from what
describe that more what energy energy
from what well it's from what have been
euphemistically referred to as the
template level reality ah I get it or
what sometimes astral plane lower astral
plane might be another euphemism for it
yet I'm going to use that word again
that's cool all right thank you you do
understand what that mej of course okay
good it's not that we're freezing down
here it's just things are cool um I
guess that's it thank thank you enjoy
your experimentation I am looking
forward to it very much we are Looking
Backward to it I bet you
are we love you our love to you as well